University of Arizona Athletics Collection 1913-2011
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
University of Arizona Athletics Collection 1913-2011
MS 564
University of Arizona Athletics Department
The University of Arizona Athletics collection, 1913-2011, consists of correspondence, athletic programs, media guides, ephemera, student handbooks, scrapbooks and the papers of Charles “Bumps” Tribolet, Graduate Manager of Student Activities.
72.15 linear feet (51 boxes, 51 scrapbooks)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Historical Note
The University of Arizona's athletic program is rooted in a strong foundation of tradition and history that dates back to the early 1900s. Men's football, baseball and basketball have been played at the University almost as long as the UA has been in existence. Under the leadership of coaches and athletics directors such as J.F. "Pop" McKale and Fred Enke the University of Arizona athletics department has enjoyed a robust history. The Wildcats' other success in softball and baseball - a combined nine NCAA titles - and the program's 1997 NCAA Championship in men's basketball underscore the level of competitiveness embraced by UA sports programs. Records from the University of Arizona athletics department were collected over many years and housed at Mckale Center until they were transferred to Special Collections in 2015.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight series:
Series I: Correspondence, 1913-1939
Series II: Programs, 1916-2011
Series III: Media Guides, 1949-2011
Series IV: Other Publications 1952-2004
Series V: Ephemera, 1926-1979
Series VI: Student Handbooks, 1923-1974, 2000
Series VII: Scrapbooks, 1918-1999
Subseries I: Atheltics, 1918-1999
Subseries II: Individuals, 1952-1989
Series VIII: Papers of Charles Tribolet, 1949-1975
Scope and Content Note
The University of Arizona Athletics Collection documents the history of men's and women's athletics from 1913-2011. It consists of correspondence, athletic programs, media guides, other publications, ephemera, student handbooks, scrapbooks, and includes the papers of Charles "Bumps" Tribolet, Graduate Manager of Student Activities. This collection represents a range of competitive athletic activities, with a strong focus on football and men's basketball from the early 20th century to the early 21st century. Series I includes bills and correspondence relating to athletic administration and other student activities from 1913-1939. Series II is comprised of athletic programs from men's and women's sporting events from 1916-2010. Series III contains media guides from 1949-2011 which document player and team information and statistics for media professionals. Series IV, Other Publications, consists of bulletins, brochures, conference programs and handbooks from 1952-2004. Series V, ephemera, contains tickets from sporting and entertainment events, bumper stickers, press passes, student identification cards and other items from 1926-1979. Series VI contains student handbooks from 1923-1974 and the year 2000. Series VII contains scrapbooks mostly comprised of newspaper clippings, yearbook clippings, photographs, and other memorabilia of individual and team sports from 1918-1999. The bulk of scrapbooks cover basketball, football, and women's athletics. Series VIII, Papers of Charles Tribolet, consist of official documents and correspondence relating to athletics administration from the office of graduate manager for student activities, Charles "Bumps" Tribolet from 1949-1975.
Related materials may be found in the following collections:
James Fred McKale Papers, AZ 284
Ina E. Gittings Collection (1890-1985), MS 283
Mary Roby Papers (1926-2012), MS 553
University of Arizona Women's Athletics and Physical Education Papers (1917-1981), MS 555
Access Terms
Enke, Fred.
McKale, J.F.
Slonaker, A.L.
Tribolet, Charles
University of Arizona -- Sports.
College Sports – Arizona -- Tucson.
Sports for Women – Arizona – Tucson.
Articles
Correspondence
Photographs
Scrapbooks
Container List
- Correspondence, 1913-1939; Series I
  This series is arranged alphabetically by last name and then by year. Contains bills regarding the publication of the Daily Wildcat from 1928-1935. Also contains the incoming and outgoing correspondence of A.H. Condron, president of the student body organization from 1916-1917, as well as meeting minutes from the student body organization. A section of the correspondence of A.H. Condron contains papers which were added to these files in 1978. General correspondence contains incoming and outgoing letters primarily to J.F. “Pop” McKale, athletic director, and A.L. Slonaker, graduate manager of student activities. The incoming and outgoing correspondence of A.L. Slonaker from 1922-1938 contains letters and bills regarding athletics administration, including equipment purchases, game scheduling with other universities, letters from prospective students, financial reports, and correspondence relating to high school athletic tournaments. Some materials dated 1926-1927 relate to the death of UA quarterback and student body president John “Button” Salmon who famously told teammates to “Bear Down”. Correspondence from Al Wichtrich, President of the Associated Students from 1938-1939 is also represented in this series.
  - Bills (1 of 3), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bills (2 of 3), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bills (3 of 3), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Condron, A.H. and Student Body Organization (1 of 3), 1913-1916, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Condron, A.H. and Student Body Organization (2 of 3), 1913-1916, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Condron, A.H. and Student Body Organization (3 of 3), 1913-1916, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence (3 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 3), 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 3), 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 3), 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 3), 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 4), 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 4), 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 4), 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 4), 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 8), 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 8), 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (13 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (14 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (15 of 15), 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (13 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (14 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (15 of 15), 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (13 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (14 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (15 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (16 of 16), 1929-1930 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 9), 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 8), 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 12), 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (13 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (14 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (15 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (16 of 16), 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 12), 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 10), 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 12), 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (1 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (2 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (3 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (4 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (5 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (6 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (7 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (8 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (9 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (10 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (11 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (12 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (13 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (14 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (15 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Slonaker, A.L., (16 of 16), 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Wichtrich, Al, (1 of 3), 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Wichtrich, Al, (2 of 3), 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Wichtrich, Al, (3 of 3), 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Programs, 1916-2011; Series II:
  This series is arranged alphabetically by sport then chronologically. Sports with both men’s and women’s teams have individual listings when present. It contains regular season programs, as well as post season, conference championship programs, and souvenir programs for certain sports.
  - Baseball, 1948, 1951-1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 1958-1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Baseball, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Baseball, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Baseball, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Baseball, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Baseball, 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Baseball, 1988-1991, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Baseball; All Pro Alumi Baseball Game, 1983-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Baseball; All Pro Alumi Baseball Game, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Baseball; All Pro Alumi Baseball Game, 1995-2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Baseball; Post Season, 1980, 1986, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Baseball; Post Season, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Baseball; Souvenir Programs, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Cross Country Championships, 1984-1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Football, 1916-1932 (Box 13a, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1934-1937 (Box 13a, Folder 2)
  - Football, 1932, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1938 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1938 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1939 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1940 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1940 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Football, 1941,-1942, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Football, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Football, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1949 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Football, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Football, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Football, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Football, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Football, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Football, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Football, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Football, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Football, 1965 (Box 15a, Folder 1)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1966 (Box 15a, Folder 2)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1966 (Box 15a, Folder 3)
  - Football, 1967 (Box 15a, Folder 4)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1968 (Box 15a, Folder 5)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Football, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Football, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Football, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Football, (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Football, (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Football, (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Football, (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Football, (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Football, (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Football, (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Football, (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Football, (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Football, (1 of 4), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Football, (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Football, (3 of 4), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Football, (4 of 4), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Football, (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Football, (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Football, (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Football, (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Football, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Football, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Football, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Football, (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Football, (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Football, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Football,(1 of 5), 2008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Football,(2 of 5), 2008 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Football,(3 of 5), 2008 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Football,(4 of 5), 2008 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Football,(5 of 5), 2008 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Football,(1 of 2), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Football,(2 of 2), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Football,(1 of 5), 2010 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Football,(2 of 5), 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Football,(3 of 5), 2010 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Football,(4 of 5), 2010 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Football,(5 of 5), 2010 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Football; Bowl Games, 1955-1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Football; Bowl Games, 1970, 1979, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Football; Bowl Games, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Football; Bowl Games, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ice Hockey, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 1942, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, 1948-1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, 1954-1957 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)